Antonio Moreno

Telephone: +55 48 98435-3437 Email: amrh07@gmail.com Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/antonio-mrh/

Github: github.com/AntonioMRH

SUMMARY

As a Bachelor in Control and Automation Engineering with 4+ years of experience in the tech industry, I have a strong foundation in software development and project management. My previous experience includes working for a consultancy firm where I helped to build and grow a software development team from 1 to 8 members in just one year. In my latest experience, I worked for a WEB3 startup where I built crypto products.

EDUCATION

Universidade Federal de Santa Catarina

July 2015 - September 2021

Bacherlor in Control and Automation Engineering

SKILLS

Software: JavaScript, Typescript, HTML, CSS, SASS, LESS, Python, SQL, React, Next.js, MySQL, Postgresql, GCP, AWS, GIT, Docker, TailwindCSS, Styled Components, Material UI, Chakra UI, Bootstrap, NPM, Node.js, ESLint, Prettier, Pixel Perfect, Jest, Cypress, React Testing Library, Scrum.

Languages: Portuguese (Native), Spanish (Native), English (Fluent).

EXPERIENCE

Hack-a-chain

Sept 2022 - December 2022

Software Engineer

- Collaborated with two other team members to create a DeFi platform on the NEAR blockchain.
- Implemented performance enhancements on the back end by updating GraphQL queries.
 - Tech Stack: React, TypeScript, TailwindCSS, Chakra UI, GraphQL, Node.js, Postgresql.

BIX Tech

May 2021 - August 2022

Software Developer

Development of Web applications and software for companies in various sectors. Participation in projects such as:

- Responsible for developing a customer section page for one of the largest ceramic tile companies in the world.
 - Tech Stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, FastAPI, Postgresql, AWS.
- Worked with a team to develop a software solution for monitoring factory processes in the agricultural sector and to build a mobile app that aids in the classification of grain quality in the field.
 - o Tech Stack: React, Material UI, Chart.js, Styled Components, GCP.
- Created a blog and advertising page for a company specializing in providing advertising services to financial sector clients. Coordinated the work of an intern during the development process.
 - o Tech Stack: Next.js, TypeScript, Material UI, GCP.

RD Station March 2019 - March 2021

Marketing Operations Intern

- Analyzed business metrics to support marketing strategy decisions and helped create metrics and KPIs.
- Assisted in constructing and implementing business processes, including restructuring chatbot flows on company website pages. This resulted in a 33% improvement in chatbot conversion rates.
- Created reports and dashboards for data visualization to track results
- Developed playbooks to map and document various processes.
 - o Tech Stack: SQL, Postgresql, Power BI, G Workspace, MS Excel, Python.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Certifications: Testing React with Jest and React Testing Library (RTL) from Udemy (2023).
- Certifications: JavaScript: The Advanced Concepts (2023 Update) from Udemy (2023).

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

AIESEC January 2017 - June 2017

Project Manager

- Trained and managed a sales team.
- Headhunted internship candidates.
- Developed and implemented strategies to achieve team goals.

Team member July 2016 - December 2016

- Contract closing with local NGOs.
- Reception and follow-up of exchange students from the global volunteering program.